{"test_questions": [[{"question": "What is the frequency range of the IEEE 802.11a standard?", "opta": "2.4Gbps", "optb": "5Gbps", "optc": "2.4GHz", "optd": "5GHz", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11a standard runs in the 5GHz RF range."}, {"question": "What is the maximum distance running the lowest data rate for 802.11b?", "opta": "About 100 feet", "optb": "About 175 feet", "optc": "About 300 feet", "optd": "About 350 feet", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11b standard provides the lowest data rate at 1Mbps, but it also has the longest distance, which is about 350 feet."}, {"question": "What is the maximum distance with maximum data rate for 802.11a?", "opta": "About 65-75 feet", "optb": "About 90-100 feet", "optc": "About 150 feet", "optd": "Over 200 feet", "ans": "A", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11a standard provides a maximum data rate of up to 54Mbps, but you need to be close to the access point, somewhere around 65 to 75 feet."}, {"question": "What is the frequency range of the IEEE 802.11b standard?", "opta": "2.4Gbps", "optb": "5Gbps", "optc": "2.4GHz", "optd": "5GHz", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11b and IEEE 802.11g standards both run in the 2.4GHz RF range."}, {"question": "You have a Cisco mesh network. What protocol allows multiple APs to connect with many redundant connections between nodes?", "opta": "LWAPP", "optb": "AWPP", "optc": "STP", "optd": "IEEE", "ans": "B", "explanation": "Each AP in a mesh network runs the Adaptive Wireless Path Protocol (AWPP). This protocol allows RAPs to communicate with each other to determine the best path back to the wired network via the RAP."}, {"question": "What is the maximum data rate for the 802.11g standard?", "opta": "6Mbps", "optb": "11Mbps", "optc": "22Mbps", "optd": "54Mbps", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11g standard provides a maximum data rate of up to 54Mbps."}, {"question": "What is the maximum data rate for the 802.11a standard?", "opta": "6Mbps", "optb": "11Mbps", "optc": "22Mbps", "optd": "54Mbps", "ans": "D", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11a standard provides a maximum data rate of up to 54Mbps."}, {"question": "How many non-overlapping channels are available with 802.11b?", "opta": "3", "optb": "12", "optc": "23", "optd": "40", "ans": "A", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11b standard provides 3 non-overlapping channels."}, {"question": "How many non-overlapping channels are available with 802.11a?", "opta": "3", "optb": "12", "optc": "23", "optd": "40", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11a standard provides up to 12 non-overlapping channels."}, {"question": "In Cisco's Unified Wireless Solution, what is the split-MAC architecture?", "opta": "The split-MAC architecture uses MAC addresses to create a forward/filter table and break up collision domains.", "optb": "The split-MAC architecture allows the splitting of 802.11 protocol packets between the AP and the controller to allow processing by both devices.", "optc": "The split-MAC architecture uses MAC addresses on the wireless network and IP addresses on the wired network.", "optd": "The split-MAC architecture uses MAC addresses to create a forward/filter table and break up broadcast domains.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The split-MAC architecture allows the splitting of 802.11 protocol packets between the Cisco LWAPP-based AP, which handles real-time portions of the protocol, and the WLAN controller, which handles those items that are not time sensitive."}, {"question": "What is the maximum distance with maximum data rate for 802.11b?", "opta": "About 65-75 feet", "optb": "About 90-100 feet", "optc": "About 150 feet", "optd": "Over 200 feet", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11b standard provides a maximum data rate of up to only 11Mbps, and you can be around 150 feet, maybe farther, depending on conditions."}, {"question": "What is the maximum distance with maximum data rate for 802.11g?", "opta": "About 65-75 feet", "optb": "About 90-100 feet", "optc": "About 150 feet", "optd": "Over 200 feet", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11g standard provides a maximum data rate of up to 54Mbps, but you need to be close to the access point, somewhere around 90 to 100 feet."}, {"question": "What is the maximum distance running the lowest data rate for 802.11a?", "opta": "About 100 feet", "optb": "About 175 feet", "optc": "About 300 feet", "optd": "About 350 feet", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11a standard's lowest data rate is 6Mbps, but it can run from a distance of about 175 feet."}, {"question": "How many non-overlapping channels are available with 802.11h?", "opta": "3", "optb": "12", "optc": "23", "optd": "40", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11h standard provides an addition 11 channels to the 802.11a standard's 12 non-overlapping channel for a total of 23 non-overlapping channels."}, {"question": "What is the maximum data rate for the 802.11b standard?", "opta": "6Mbps", "optb": "11Mbps", "optc": "22Mbps", "optd": "54Mbps", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11b standard provides a maximum data rate of up to 11Mbps."}, {"question": "You are connecting your access point and it is set to root. What does Extended Service Set ID mean?", "opta": "That you have more than one access point and they are in the same SSID connected by a distribution system.", "optb": "That you have more than one access point and they are in separate SSIDs connected by a distribution system.", "optc": "That you have multiple access points, but they are placed physically in different buildings.", "optd": "That you have multiple access points, but one is a repeater access point.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "Extended Service Set ID means that you have more than one access point and they all are set to the same SSID and all are connected together in the same VLAN or distribution system so users can roam."}, {"question": "Cisco's Unified Wireless Solution provides a mesh solution. What devices do you absolutely need to purchase to run a Cisco solution?\n  WCS\n  Controller\n  Access point\n  Bridge", "opta": "1 and 2", "optb": "2 and 3", "optc": "1 and 4 only", "optd": "4 only", "ans": "B", "explanation": "The Cisco Unified Wireless Solution is a great product, but you must purchase specialized devices. Cisco managed access points and a controller are the devices you need to purchase to run the Unified Wireless Solution."}, {"question": "What is the frequency range of the IEEE 802.11g standard?", "opta": "2.4Gbps", "optb": "5Gbps", "optc": "2.4GHz", "optd": "5GHz", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11b and IEEE 802.11g standards both run in the 2.4GHz RF range."}, {"question": "How many non-overlapping channels are available with 802.11g?", "opta": "3", "optb": "12", "optc": "23", "optd": "40", "ans": "A", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11g standard provides 3 non-overlapping channels."}, {"question": "What is the maximum distance running the lowest data rate for 802.11g?", "opta": "About 100 feet", "optb": "About 175 feet", "optc": "About 300 feet", "optd": "About 350 feet", "ans": "C", "explanation": "The IEEE 802.11g standard's lowest data rate is 6Mbps, but it can run from a distance of about 300 feet."}]]}